Technology is developing by leaps and bounds.
科技正飞速发展。
A gadget as small as a smartphone now has more processing power than rockets to the Moon once had.
如今一部小小的智能手机，其处理能力甚至超过了当年用于登月的火箭。
New tech brings many advantages, making our lives easier and opening up new opportunities.
新技术带来诸多益处，既让我们的生活变得更加便捷，也开拓了全新的发展机遇。
One piece of kit that’s been really taking off recently is the drone.
近年来，一种设备的热度持续攀升，那就是无人机。
This pilotless mini aircraft, originally developed for aerial photography and warfare, is now bringing us benefits closer to home.
这种无人驾驶的小型飞行器最初是为航空摄影和军事用途研发的，如今正为我们的日常生活带来实实在在的好处。
In the last few years, tech companies such as Amazon, Alphabet and Uber have promised us delivery drones – bringing goods to our doorsteps in a matter of minutes.
过去几年里，亚马逊、字母表公司和优步等科技企业都曾承诺推出配送无人机——能在短短几分钟内将商品送到我们家门口。
Progress in developing them has, however, been slow.
不过，这类无人机的研发进程却较为缓慢。
Drones are helping to connect with and enhance the lives of people in remote locations.
无人机正助力偏远地区的人们加强联系、改善生活。
In the UK, the Royal Mail wants a fleet of 500 drones to help deliver the mail to far-flung communities.
在英国，皇家邮政计划配备一支由500架无人机组成的机队，为偏远社区提供邮件配送服务。
Windracers, the company developing the drones, say they can fly in fog and produce 30% fewer emissions than comparable piloted aircraft.
负责研发这些无人机的风行者公司表示，该款无人机能够在大雾天气飞行，其排放量比同类有人驾驶飞行器减少30%。
And in Coventry in the UK, construction has started on an air hub, which will act as a base for police and delivery drones.
此外，在英国考文垂市，一个航空枢纽的建设工程已经启动，这里将成为警用无人机和配送无人机的基地。
Urban-Air Port Limited is working with car-maker Hyundai on the mini-airport, known as a skyport.
城市空中港有限公司正与汽车制造商现代合作打造这座被称为“空中港”的小型机场。
Drones could also play a part in improving the health of millions of people.
无人机还能为改善数百万人的健康状况贡献力量。
In Zanzibar, for example, they’re being used to spray wetlands against malaria.
例如在桑给巴尔，无人机被用于在湿地喷洒药剂，防控疟疾。
And writing for BBC Future website, Harriet Constable describes an incredible development project by the University of South Australia.
哈里特·康斯特布尔在为BBC未来频道撰稿时，介绍了南澳大利亚大学一个令人瞩目的研发项目。
The plan is for drones to eventually be able to survey populations for disease by reading the blood oxygen levels of humans from the air.
该项目计划让无人机最终能够从空中读取人体的血氧水平，以此对人群进行疾病筛查。
They’ll also be able to scan for other vital signs, like coughing and a high temperature.
无人机还将能够侦测咳嗽、高烧等其他生命体征。
It seems the sky’s the limit for what drone technology can achieve.
无人机技术的发展潜力似乎无穷无尽。
The only thing that sometimes keeps it grounded is regulation.
有时唯一制约它发展的因素就是监管政策。
Writing for the BBC, Jessica Brown says: “If our skies are to become as crowded as our streets, airspace rules need updating to prevent accidents.”
杰西卡·布朗在为BBC撰稿时表示：“若想让天空变得像街道一样繁忙，就必须更新空域管理规则，以避免事故发生。”
There are also related problems, such as noise pollution.
此外，无人机还存在噪音污染等相关问题。